[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Alfred Smith Dinner"]}, "docId": "121018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "What are we about to see?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "we", "about", "to", "see", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "The Alfred Smith Dinner here in just a few moments from now.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "Alfred", "Smith", "Dinner", "here", "in", "just", "a", "few", "moments", "from", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "121018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "Gloria, why do these candidates normally attend this event sponsored by the Archdiocese of New York?", "question_tokens": ["Gloria", ",", "why", "do", "these", "candidates", "normally", "attend", "this", "event", "sponsored", "by", "the", "Archdiocese", "of", "New", "York", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "I think at this point in the campaign, Wolf, it's clear to them and it's also pretty clear to us that what we need is some civility, a little bit of humor.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "at", "this", "point", "in", "the", "campaign", ",", "Wolf", ",", "it", "'s", "clear", "to", "them", "and", "it", "'s", "also", "pretty", "clear", "to", "us", "that", "what", "we", "need", "is", "some", "civility", ",", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "humor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Don't you agree?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "you", "agree", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "I would imagine so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "imagine", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ross", "Barack Obama", "John McCain"]}, "docId": "121018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "What do you think is going to happen in the course of the next hour?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "is", "going", "to", "happen", "in", "the", "course", "of", "the", "next", "hour", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "Well, I think that Ross actually made a very interesting point because if you remember, Barack Obama and John McCain actually used to be friends.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "Ross", "actually", "made", "a", "very", "interesting", "point", "because", "if", "you", "remember", ",", "Barack", "Obama", "and", "John", "McCain", "actually", "used", "to", "be", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this evening"]}, "docId": "121018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "How is preparing to tell some jokes?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "preparing", "to", "tell", "some", "jokes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Well, you know, I think they're being pretty tightlipped about the material that we're going to be hearing later on this evening.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "think", "they", "'re", "being", "pretty", "tightlipped", "about", "the", "material", "that", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "be", "hearing", "later", "on", "this", "evening", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "Cadeau?", "question_tokens": ["Cadeau", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "121018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "WRB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Is that what it is?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "it", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "You know, one thing I'm reminded of, Wolf, is how important presidential joke writers are.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "one", "thing", "I", "'m", "reminded", "of", ",", "Wolf", ",", "is", "how", "important", "presidential", "joke", "writers", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "What did you think, Gloria?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", ",", "Gloria", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "I thought he was funny.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "he", "was", "funny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gloria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Gloria, what did you think?", "question_tokens": ["Gloria", ",", "what", "did", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "I thought he was funny.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "he", "was", "funny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "How did they do?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "they", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "I -- I agree with the whole panel.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "agree", "with", "the", "whole", "panel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Don't you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "Yes, I look forward to wearing those white ties.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "look", "forward", "to", "wearing", "those", "white", "ties", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "121018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Were you surprised by this poll?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "surprised", "by", "this", "poll", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "I was surprised by that poll, Wolf.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "surprised", "by", "that", "poll", ",", "Wolf", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Were you surprised by that?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "surprised", "by", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "No, those were the numbers you would expect to see.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "those", "were", "the", "numbers", "you", "would", "expect", "to", "see", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tanya", "Romney"]}, "docId": "121018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "And the question is, will it pay off?", "question_tokens": ["And", "the", "question", "is", ",", "will", "it", "pay", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "And you see new ads from the Romney campaign, Tanya, right now stressing the fact that Romney believes there should be exceptions.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "you", "see", "new", "ads", "from", "the", "Romney", "campaign", ",", "Tanya", ",", "right", "now", "stressing", "the", "fact", "that", "Romney", "believes", "there", "should", "be", "exceptions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]